xtratime.org 2010-05-07

# Xtratime Community : Privacy policy

## Privacy policy

Xtratime respects your privacy, and we would like to assure you that we are deeply committed in protecting the privacy of our visitors. The information that you provide us with, or the information that is automatically gathered, helps us, as well as third parties to monitor our service and provide you with better services. Please note, however, that any personal information that you submit in the forums or by email for publication may be collected by others. If you have any comments, questions, or suggestions, feel free to email us from the contact page.

### Registration

If you choose, you may register at Xtratime. This is a one time event and once you register, you can use the forums. This is not compulsory. For your own sake, do not post personal information in the forums, because it can be seen by virtually anybody. The information you supply is in no way used for sending you newsletters or promotions unless stated. Most of all, please make sure you read the rules, which state your rights in the forums. 

### Cookies

We use 'cookies' to track advertising information and website usage, such as browser types, platform, etc. This information helps us provide you with better services. For example, cookies limit the number of times you see the same ad. 

### Surveys 

Occasionally, we may have online surveys. These are optional and in no way mandatory. Surveys help us collect demographic information to help us see how we're doing. Non-personal information may be shared with third parties. 

### Newsletters 

We have a free e-mail newsletter. All that we ask of you is your email address. Our email list will not be given to third parties unless we have your consent. There may be advertisements in them, however, of services we offer. Subscribing from the newsletters is very easy: simply type in your email address in the box provided and check "Unsubscribe." 

### Security 

While we aim to keep the information you supply us with directly or indirectly secure, please be aware that the Internet is not fully secure. 

### Competitions and Promotions

From time to time, Xtratime may operate competitions and promotions. Participation in these is completely optional. Submitted information may be given to third parties. 

### Use of information 

Upon legal issues arising from a matter (i.e. information posted in the forums), we have the right to submit your information to local or government authorities. 

## Policy changes 

Any changes to this policy may occur at any time on this same page.
